<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Acadia 2021</title>
    <link>http://2021.acadia.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Acadia 2021</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://2021.acadia.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Admission</title>
      <link>http://2021.acadia.org/admission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://2021.acadia.org/admission/</guid>
      <description>Applying to the Master of Arts, Human Experience Design Interactions Program
For detailed information please visit our Admissions Page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faculty</title>
      <link>http://2021.acadia.org/faculty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://2021.acadia.org/faculty/</guid>
      <description>FACULTY HXDI
Heather BarkerInterim Chair, Associate Professor of Design, Graduate Coordinator Department Chair, Tenured, Faculty
Heather Renée Barker, Associate Professor of Design at California State University Long Beach is a human urbanist. She works with interdisciplinary teams to facilitate human-centered approaches to improving the human/data hybrid experience. By leveraging a range of analog and digital tools gamification, and data-visualization, Heather brings value to business and civic organizations as they develop novel solutions to personal interface, animated space, community engagement, and sustainable urban challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selected Projects</title>
      <link>http://2021.acadia.org/selected-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://2021.acadia.org/selected-projects/</guid>
      <description>ABOUT SELECTED PROJECTS
The HXDI selected projects include interdisciplinary works which spans across scales, mediums, theory and practice. Students engages with AI Deep Learning Algorithms, Physical Computing, Algorithmic Design, 360 Videos, VR, AR, Creative Coding and Immersive Installations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Students</title>
      <link>http://2021.acadia.org/students/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://2021.acadia.org/students/</guid>
      <description>ABOUT COHORT
The HXDI cohort is composed of students from vast educational and professional backgrounds. Because of their diversity each project completed is unique and displays their skillsets, experiences and passions. This diverseness helps shape their cohort dynamic and program.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
